Inventory of the Mills E. Godwin Jr. Papers 1947-1989
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Speeches, 1957-1978. (Box 17-24)
  - Speeches, 1976., 140 items. (Box 22-23)
    - Savings Bond Drive Meeting, Highway Auditorium Richmond, Virginia, 25 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Second Statewide Conference on Volunteerism, Richmond Hyatt House, 26 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Commonwealth Day Dinner, John Marshall Hotel, 27 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Opening of the Yorktown Victory Center, Yorktown, Virginia, 1 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - TODAY Show Filming - Notes, 2 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Corporate Patrons, Tenth Anniversary Party, Virginia Museum, Richmond, Virginia, 3 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Savings Bond Drive Meeting, Highway Auditorium Richmond, Virginia, 4 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Eastern Regional Bank Administration Institute Convention, Norfolk Scope, Norfolk, Virginia, 5 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the Hollister Incorporated Plant Stuarts Draft, Virginia, 9 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication, Western Virginia Bicentennial Center, Charlottesville, Virginia, 13 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Introduction of Mrs. Francine I. Neff, Treasurer of the United States and National Director, U. S. Savings Bonds Division, University of Virginia Rotunda, 13 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Appreciation Dinner, VMI Keydet Clubs, Commonwealth Club, Richmond, Virginia, 14 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the Shenandoah Valley Plant, Johns-Manville Corporation, 15 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Adjutant General Association of the United States, Hospitality House, Williamsburg, Virginia, 19 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - DAR Convention, Constitution Hall, Washington, D. C., 19 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Opening of Bicentennial Observances, Stratford Hall Plantation, Stratford, Virginia, 25 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of Hon Industries Plant, Chesterfield County Building, 28 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Masonic Bicentennial Observance, The Mosque, Richmond, Virginia, 29 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Twenty-eighth National Convention, Widows of World War I, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 30 April 1976. (Box 22)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, Loyalty Day, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Buckingham County Day, Buckingham County High School, 1 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Poultry Convention, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 14 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Scotchtown Bicentennial Celebration, 15 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Commencement, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, 16 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Welcome to President Valery Giscard d'Estaing, Yorktown, Virginia, 19 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Room 3106, Dirkson Senate office Building, Washington, D. C., 20 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia World Trade Day Luncheon, Hotel John Marshall, 20 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Introduction of Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Greek Ancestry Dinner, 22 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Mid-Atlantic National Rehabilitation Association Conference, Omni International Hotel, Norfolk, Virginia, 23 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Southeastern Association of Regulatory Utility Commissioners, Williamsburg, 25 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Governor's Council on Transportation, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 28 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Patrick Henry Day, Brookneal, Virginia, 29 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Northumberland County Bicentennial Memorial Service, Northumberland County Courthouse, Heathsville, Virginia, 31 May 1976. (Box 22)
    - Southern Region School Boards Association, Conference Center, Williamsburg, Virginia, 4 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Excerpts from remarks, Republican State Convention, Norfolk, Virginia, 5 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - ABC Warehouse Dedication, 9 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Harry Flood Byrd Memorial Dedication, Capitol Square, 10 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of The Clarendon Bank and Trust Headquarters Building, Arlington, Virginia, 10 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - George Mason Lectures, Williamsburg, Virginia, 12 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Mount Vernon High School Commencement, 14 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Southern Regional Education Board, Peachtree Plaza Hotel, Atlanta, Georgia, 16 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the Mobile Youth Center, Roanoke, Virginia, 19 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Appreciation Dinner for Dr. Leroy Smith, 21 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Billy Graham Bicentennial Festival of Faith, William and Mary Hall, Williamsburg, Virginia, 24 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Awards Luncheon, Statewide Bicentennial, Patrick Henry Oratorical Contest, Great Hall, William and Mary College, Williamsburg, Virginia, 29 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - 200th Anniversary of the Founding of the Commonwealth Massie Building, Fairfax County, 29 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Change of Command Ceremony, Navy Recruiting District, Navy Marine Reserve Center, Richmond, 30 June 1976. (Box 22)
    - Ribbon Cutting, Statewide Bicentennial Flower Show, Roanoke Civic Center, 2 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Montgomery County Bicentennial Commemoration, Blacksburg, Virginia, 2 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the United States Army Transportation Museum, Fort Eustis, Virginia, 9 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Response by the governor to Queen's Comments, Cabell Hall, University of Virginia, 10 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the Mannboro Medical Center Limited, Amelia County, Virginia, 11 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Bankers Association, Convention at the Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 14 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Pittsylvania Bicentennial Program, Hurt, Virginia, 16 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Kiwanis Clubs of Richmond, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 19 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia's Spruce Up Campaign Luncheon, Reynolds Wrap Distribution Center, Richmond, Virginia, 20 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Southeastern Aviation Trades Association, The Hospitality House, Williamsburg, Virginia, 22 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Southern Regional Education Board, Legislative Work Conference, Annapolis Hilton Inn, Annapolis, Maryland, 29 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Introduction of Colgate Darden, First Assembly Day, Jamestown, Virginia, 30 July 1976. (Box 22)
    - Speech seconding nomination of President Ford, Republican National Convention, Kansas City, 18 August 1976. (Box 22)
    - Southern Governors' Conference, Williamsburg, Virginia Opening Remarks, 30 August 1976. (Box 22)
    - Report on Southern Regional Education Board, Southern Governors' Conference, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication Greenville Memorial Hospital Addition, Emporia, Virginia, 7 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Annual Safety Awards Luncheon, 9 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Presentation of Silver Service Commissioning Ceremony, U. S. S. Virginia, Norfolk, Virginia, 11 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Times Newspapers Luncheon, London, England, 21 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, Williamsburg, Virginia, 24 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Richmond County Bicentennial Celebration, Warsaw, Virginia, 25 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - United Way Kickoff for State Agency Heads, State Highway Auditorium, Richmond, Virginia, 27 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - State Fair Luncheon, 28 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - White House of the Confederacy, Richmond, Virginia, 29 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the Exchange Hotel, Gordonsville, Virginia, 30 September 1976. (Box 22)
    - Public Hearing on I-66 Modifications, Washington, D. C., 2 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Friends of the Industry of Agriculture Cooperative Month Breakfast, Valle's Steak House, Richmond, Virginia, 5 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Introduction of Senator Dole, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 5 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Presentation of Thomas Jefferson Award to James J. Kilpatrick, Public Relations Society of America, Hotel John Marshall, 5 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlantic States Marine Fisheries Commission, Hospitality House, Williamsburg, Virginia, 6 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Unveiling of the Portrait of Chief Justice Eggleston, Supreme Court Building, 7 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - George J. Oliver Hall Dedication, Virginia Commonwealth University, 9 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Albemarle County Republican Committee's Annual Grand old Pig Roast, Charlottesville, Virginia, 9 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of Birdsall-Hoover Building, Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, Fishersville, Virginia, 12 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - World Trade Conference, Omni Hotel, Norfolk, Virginia, 14 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of the Mixing Equipment Company Division, Wytheville, Virginia, 15 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Dedication of Statue of Admiral De Grasse, Fort Story Officers' Club, 17 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Welcome to Virginia for the International Association of Milk Control Agencies, Quality Inn, Fort Magruder, Williamsburg, Virginia, 18 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Surrender Day Ceremonies, Gloucester County, Virginia, Institute of Marine Science Campus, 18 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Yorktown Day, Yorktown, Virginia, 19 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia National Bank, Eighth and Main Streets, Richmond, Virginia, 20 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - National Association of State Aviation Officials, Omni Hotel, Norfolk, Virginia, 21 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Mount Vernon Regency Luncheon, Mount Vernon, Virginia, 22 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Introduction of President Gerald R. Ford, State Capitol, Richmond, Virginia, 23 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Response by the governor after Message by President Gerald R. Ford, State Capitol, Richmond, Virginia, 23 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Goochland Baptist Church, 24 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Travel Writer's Luncheon, New York, New York, 27 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Report to Top Management, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York, New York, 28 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Annual Meeting, Virginia Community Colleges, Williamsburg, Virginia, 29 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - A.S.M.E. Conference, Williamsburg, Virginia, 31 October 1976. (Box 22)
    - Highway and Transportation Conference, Virginia Military Institute, 4 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Testimonial Dinner for Congressman and Mrs. Thomas N. Downing, Hampton Coliseum, 5 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Governor's Day, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Virginia, 6 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Re-enactment of the First Thanksgiving, Berkeley Plantation, 7 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Joint Meeting House Appropriations and Finance Committees, Senate Finance Committee, House Chamber, 8 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - 82nd National Conference on Government, National Municipal League, Williamsburg, Virginia, 8 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - 83rd Annual Convention of the United Daughters of the Confederacy, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 8 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - 50th Anniversary of Colonial Williamsburg, 12 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Commerce and Resources Agency Heads and Board Members, F & M Center, Richmond, 22 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Annual Service Club Luncheon Alexandria Chamber of Commerce, Ramada Inn, Alexandria, Virginia, 24 November 1976. (Box 23)
    - Farm Bureau Federation Convention, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 2 December 1976. (Box 23)
    - Seminar, Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 3 December 1976. (Box 23)
    - Brotherhood Citation Dinner, Richmond Chapter - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, 8 December 1976. (Box 23)
    - Third Grade Students of St. Christopher's and St. Catherine's Schools on the occasion of George Mason's Birthday, State Capitol, 10 December 1976. (Box 23)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, 16 December 1976. (Box 23)
  - Speeches, 1977., 146 items. (Box 23-24)
    - , 1977. (Box 23)
    - Opening of Discovery Room, Virginia Science Museum, Broad Street Station, 6 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Address to the General Assembly, 12 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Commonwealth Prayer Breakfast, John Marshall Hotel, 13 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Welcome to Atlantic Companies Computer Center, Roanoke, Virginia, 18 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Council of Churches Prayer Breakfast, St. Paul's Church, 19 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Appreciation Banquet, State Fairgrounds, 19 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful Awards Luncheon, Hotel John Marshall, 26 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Presentation of the President's "E" Award to Virginia State Ports Authority, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 26 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction Justice Lewis F. Powell, Dedication John Marshall Courts Building, 30 January 1977. (Box 23)
    - Bicentennial Debates Awards Dinner, Williamsburg, Virginia, 11 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction of Carter O. Lowance, Charter Day Ceremony, College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, 12 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Remarks by the governor in response to Owen Cheatham, Virginia Museum Dinner for Owen Cheatham Foundation, 12 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Grand Lodge Communication Masonic Order, Hotel John Marshall, 14 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Annual Conservation Forum of The Garden Club Luncheon, St. Paul's Episcopal Church, 14 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Midwinter Conference of the American Correctional Association, Virginia Beach, 18 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Groundbreaking, Stihl Corporation, Oceana West Industrial Park, Virginia Beach, 18 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Carlyle House, Alexandria, Virginia, 20 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - The First Virginia Regiment of the Continental Line for their re-enactment, 20 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Wreath Laying Ceremony, George Washington Birthday Celebration, 20 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - Inaugural Address, Old Dominion University, 26 February 1977. (Box 23)
    - To the members of the General Assembly at end of session, 4 March 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction of John N. Dalton, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, 7 March 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication of the Onduline Plant, Massaponac, Virginia, 17 March 1977. (Box 23)
    - Maiden Voyage of Columbus Virginia, Portsmouth Marine Terminal, 21 March 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication of New Board Room, Mountain Security Savings and Loan Association, Wytheville, Virginia, 28 March 1977. (Box 23)
    - Wytheville, Wythe-Bland Chamber of Commerce, Wytheville Community Center, 28 March 1977. (Box 23)
    - School Superintendents Conference, Hotel Roanoke, 4 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Testimony by the governor before the Subcommittee on Economic Development and Regional Affairs, Committee on the District of Columbia, House of Representatives, 5 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Council of Bishops, United Methodist Church, Williamsburg, Virginia, 13 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Chambers of Commerce Prince William County and Greater Manassas, 14 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Conference for Children, Henderson Middle School, Richmond, 15 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Model General Assembly, State Capitol, 15 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Operating Room Supervisors Conference, Williamsburg, Virginia, 16 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Amherst County Chamber of Commerce, Winton Country Club, Clifford, Virginia (speech given by Mr. Maurice B. Rowe, Secretary of Administration and Finance), 20 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary, Virginia Beach Rotary Club, cavalier Yacht and Country Club, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 21 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication of Phase I. Mecklenburg Maximum Security Facility, 22 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary James Monroe Memorial Foundation, James Monroe Law Office, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 25 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Keydet Club, Appreciation Dinner, 26 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Centennial Dinner, Department of Agriculture and Commerce, Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 27 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Statewide Meeting of Volunteer Groups Concerned with Crime Reduction, St. Bridget's Rectory, 27 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Banquet in Honor of Otis Brown, Hyatt House, 28 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication of the Vinton Firehouse, 30 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dogwood Festival, Vinton War Memorial, 30 April 1977. (Box 23)
    - Tenth Anniversary, Central Virginia Community College, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - State Agency Luncheon, John Marshall Hotel, 2 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Annual Conference, Virginia Safety Association, Roanoke Hotel, Roanoke, Virginia, 4 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication of the Exchange Hotel, Gordonsville, Virginia, 5 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Annual Luncheon, Virginia Council on State Legislation, Scott Hall, St. Paul's Church, Richmond, 11 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Mortgage Bankers Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 13 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Two Hundredth Anniversary of Powhatan County, Courthouse Square, Powhatan, 14 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - VMI Commencement, 15 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - National Alcoholic Beverage Control Association, Americana Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida, 16 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Night, National Press Club, Washington, D. C., 18 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Third Statewide Volunteerism Conference, William and Mary Student Center, Williamsburg, 20 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Acceptance of Award, World Trade Luncheon, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, 23 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Annual Meeting, Virginia Retail Merchants Association, The Homestead, 23 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - National Association of Tax Administrators, 31 May 1977. (Box 23)
    - Third Annual Public Information Workshop, Auditorium Department of Highways and Transportation, 3 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication Alfred Teves, Incorporated, Culpeper, Virginia, 3 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction, Governor Raymond Philip Shafer, 3 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction of Republican Candidate, GOP Convention, 4 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Commencement Address, Collegiate Schools, 9 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Statement at unveiling of Portrait of the Honorable Claude Vernon Spratley (by Carter Lowance in the governor's absence), 9 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Greetings to The Virginia International Women's Meeting, University of Richmond, Robins Center, 10 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Commencement, Suffolk High School, 10 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - American Legion Boy's State, Lynchburg College, 13 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - 60th Annual Membership Meeting, Richmond Chapter, American National Red Cross, St. Paul's Church, 15 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Commissioning Ceremony, Bird International Corporation, Lynchburg, Virginia, 17 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Fluvanna Bicentennial Celebration, Fluvanna County High School, 18 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Groundbreaking for New Hospital, Medical College of Virginia, 12th and Marshall Streets, Richmond, Virginia, 20 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Fund Raising Luncheon, Northern Virginia Training Center, 21 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Chairman's Report, SREB Annual Meeting, Houston, Texas, 23 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction of Christopher C. Kraft, Jr., Southern Regional Education Board Meeting, Warwick Hotel, Houston, Texas, 23 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture, Hospitality House, Williamsburg, 28 June 1977. (Box 23)
    - Opening of I-77 at State Line, 1 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Metro Blue Line, Opening Day Ceremony, 4 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Family Resources Conference, Virginia Extension Homemakers Council, VPI and State University, Blacksburg, 13 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Seminar on Corrections, Hyatt House, Richmond, 14 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Farewell Dinner, Governor's School for the Gifted, Mary Washington College, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 15 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Press Association Luncheon, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 16 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Fifty-Ninth Annual Department Convention Banquet, American Legion, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, 16 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Introduction Admiral Jungius, First Assembly Day, Jamestown Island, 30 July 1977. (Box 23)
    - Soil Conservation Society of America, Hotel John Marshall, 8 August 1977. (Box 23)
    - Opening Remarks, Special News Conference, Southern Governors' Conference, Texas, 25 August 1977. (Box 23)
    - Annual Board Meeting, Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, Donaldson-Brown Conference Center, Blacksburg, Virginia, 25 August 1977. (Box 23)
    - Annual Safety Awards Luncheon, Richmond Hyatt House, 6 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - Dedication Ceremony Walter Reed Memorial Hospital, Gloucester, Virginia, 11 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - Women of First Presbyterian Church, 13 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginians for Bonds Kickoff, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, 14 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - United Givers Kickoff, 26 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - Council of Visitors, James Madison University, 26 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Cultural Laureate Center Award Ceremony and Dinner, 29 September 1977. (Box 23)
    - Salem/Roanoke County Chamber of Commerce, Salem Civic Center, 4 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Free Enterprise Seminar, Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, Jefferson Hotel, 4 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Shenandoah County Rotary Club, W. W. Robinson School, Woodstock, Virginia, 5 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Legal Forum, University of Virginia, 6 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Wakefield 75th Anniversary Celebration, 9 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Winchester Rotary Club, 13 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Thomas Jefferson Award Dinner, Jefferson Hotel, Richmond, 14 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Golden Wings Over Richmond, Byrd Field, 15 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Golden Wings over Richmond Dinner, Hotel Jefferson, Richmond, 15 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Opening Virginia Sports Hall of Fame, Portsmouth, Virginia, 16 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Dedication Batten Arts and Letters Building, Old Dominion University, 17 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Breakfast for Dalton, Petersburg, Virginia, 17 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Kiwanis Club, Petersburg, Virginia, 18 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Health Care Cost Seminar, Richmond Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 19 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Commonwealth Woman's Club, West End Community Center, Richmond, 19 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Barbecue for Dalton, Chesapeake, Virginia, 19 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Dalton Dinner, Chamberlin Hotel, 19 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Brockway Glass Company, Inc., Plant Ground Breaking, Danville, Virginia, 21 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Luncheon for Dalton, King of the Sea Restaurant, Danville, 21 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Dinner for John Dalton, Ramada Inn, Route 7 Beltway, Tyson's Corner, 21 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Brunch for Dalton, Sheraton Inn, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 22 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Introduction of Justice Powell, The Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities, 22 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Dedication, Nursing Education Building, Highlands Community College, 23 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Virginians for Dalton, Reception-Dinner, La Petite France, 23 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Luncheon for John Dalton, Boar's Head Inn, Charlottesville, 24 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Dedication Ceremonies, Merck Sharp & Dohme Pharmaceutical Laboratories, Elkton, Virginia, 25 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Norfolk Civic Clubs, Norfolk Scope, Norfolk, Virginia, 26 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - Highway and Transportation Conference, Lexington, Virginia, 27 October 1977. (Box 24)
    - National Institute of Municipal Law Officers, Williamsburg, Virginia, 31 October 1977. (Box 24)